Guide to the Institute on the Arts and Civic Dialogue Archive 1997-2000 MSS 127 MSS 127
© 2012 Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series 2: 1999
  - Subseries 2.7: Artist Applications
    - Karrer, Lisa, 1999 (Box 6, Folder 467)
    - Katz, Joel, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 468)
    - Kelly, Nancy, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 469)
    - Kim-Gibson, Dai Sil, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 470)
    - Kreidwise, Shirley, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 471)
    - Lanzillotto, Annie, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 472)
    - Lawson, Thomas, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 473a)
    - Lewis, Robin, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 473b)
    - Ligorano, Reese, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 474)
    - Lipper, Joanna, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 475)
    - Litoff, Jacob, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 476)
    - Loring, Sondra, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 477)
    - Lowenstein, Mark, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 478)
    - Martin, Renita, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 479)
    - Mason, Keith Antar, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 480)
    - Mayo, Lisa; Dunn, Liz, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 481)
    - McLeod, Laurie, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 482)
    - Medow, Zachary, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 483)
    - Michelman, Elizabeth, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 484)
    - Miller, Tim, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 485)
    - Minuchin-Hargaden, Jean, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 486)
    - Misurell-Mitchell, Janice, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 487)
    - Morris, Tracie, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 488)
    - Myers, Rita, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 489)
    - Nicholson, Patricia, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 490)
    - Nunez, Mariella, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 491)
    - Oakes, Michael, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 492)
    - Obenauf, Meg, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 493)
    - Ortiz, Pablo, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 494)
    - Owen, Kari Ann, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 495)
    - Parkenson, Michelle, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 496)
    - Pearson, Sara, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 498)
    - Pimsler, Stuart, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 499)
    - Plastow, Jane, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 500)
    - Portillo, Rose, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 501)
    - Ramos, Chris D.C., 1999 (Box 7, Folder 502)
    - Reeder, Roberta, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 503)
    - Reedus, Marcus, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 504)
    - Rivera, Alex, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 505)
    - Rogers, Alva, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 506)
    - Rogovin, Janice, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 507)
    - Rosenblatt, Julia, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 508)
    - Sanchez-Padilla, Beva, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 509)
    - Schulman, Sarah, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 510)
    - Schuster, Irene, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 511)
    - Shipley, Sharyn Abramhoff, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 512)
    - Siebert, Mary, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 513)
    - Skaggs, Sarah, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 514)
    - Smith, Cauleen, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 515)
    - Soe, Valerie, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 516)
    - Sparx, Anne Sullivan; Sparx, Joan, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 517)
    - Spotted Eagle, Chris, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 518)
    - Storey, Rachel, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 519)
    - Strom, Mary Ellen, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 520)
    - Swados, Liz, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 521)
    - Tajiri, Rea, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 522)
    - Tanaka, Janice, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 523)
    - Theater Labyrinth; Raymond Bobgan, Holly Holsinger, Brett Keyser, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 524)
    - Tran, T Kim-Trang, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 525)
    - Tran, Kim-Trang, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 526)
    - Varela, William, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 527)
    - Vinao, Monica, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 528)
    - Walsh, Jack, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 529)
    - Washington, Booker T., Jr., 1999 (Box 7, Folder 530)
    - Washington, Keith, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 531)
    - White, Elisa Joy, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 532)
    - Williams, Nik, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 533)
    - Wise, Debra, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 534)
    - Wright, Jules, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 535)
    - Wyrrick, Sharon, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 536)
    - Yearby, Marlies, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 538)
  - Subseries 2.8: Scholar Applications
    Applications from scholars for the 1999 session of the Institute, arranged alphabetically by last name.
    - Call to Scholars, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 539)
    - Scholars' Applications, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 540)
    - Aguero, Kathleen, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 541)
    - Arrigo, Jean Maria, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 542)
    - Barnatt, Rosalina, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 543)
    - Bergmann, Linda, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 544)
    - Bulik, Robert, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 545)
    - Breines, Wini, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 546)
    - Carrington Ross, Dorothy, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 547)
    - Chansky, Dorothy, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 548)
    - Cohen, Michael, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 549)
    - Concannon, Celia, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 550)
    - Cott, Nancy, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 551)
    - Daufin, E.K., 1999 (Box 7, Folder 552)
    - DeTurk, Sabrina, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 553)
    - Doyle, Jennifer, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 554)
    - Crawford, Neta, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 555)
    - Davidson, Mary, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 556)
    - Davis, Dale T., 1999 (Box 7, Folder 557)
    - Farris, Phoebe, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 558)
    - Fernando, Fleurette, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 559)
    - Flanagan, Constance, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 560)
    - Garton, Jane, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 561)
    - Garbor, Marjorie, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 562)
    - Golden, Renny, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 563)
    - Hafrey, Leigh, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 564)
    - Halley, Jean, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 565)
    - Hammer, E.S., 1999 (Box 7, Folder 566)
    - Harper, Walter, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 567)
    - Ishiboshi, Jean, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 568)
    - Jacobsen, Gail, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 569)
    - Jeffries, Judson, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 570)
    - Jones, Joni L., 1999 (Box 7, Folder 571)
    - Johnson, Gerard, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 572)
    - Katzew, Adrianna, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 573)
    - King, Sandra, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 574)
    - Laurence, Patricia, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 575)
    - Levan, Lori, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 576)
    - Manning, Linda, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 577)
    - Mermelstein, Egon, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 578)
    - Minow, Martha, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 579)
    - Murray, Mary, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 580)
    - Mustafa, Hudita, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 581)
    - Nieves-Squires, Sarah, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 582)
    - Pagnani, Robert L., 1999 (Box 7, Folder 583)
    - Petrites, Cynthia, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 584)
    - Reid-Merritt, Patricia, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 585)
    - Robinson, Jontyle, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 586)
    - Rosovsky, Candace, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 587)
    - Roy, Donald, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 588)
    - Russell, Susan, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 589)
    - Salomone, Rosemary, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 590a)
    - Siegel, Marc, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 590b)
    - Simon, Lisa, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 591)
    - Smith, Valerie Rae, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 592)
    - Solinger, Richie, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 593)
    - Speiser, Phillip, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 594)
    - Sullivan, Megan, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 595)
    - Trachtenberg, Barbara, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 596)
    - Travis, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 597)
    - Uscher, Nancy, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 598)
    - Warren, Clay, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 599)
    - Weiss, Daniel, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 600)
    - White, Lucie, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 601)
    - Wilkinson Duran, Nicole, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 602)
    - Wilkinson-Meyer, Jimmy, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 603)
    - Williams, Regina, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 604)
    - Winstead, William, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 605)
    - Wooten, Linda, 1999 (Box 7, Folder 606)
  - Subseries 2.9: Ancillary Artist Application
    Ancillary artist candidates were either applicants who made it past a preliminary screening or who were being considered for other types of roles within the summer session. In any case, these files were preserved as a separate corpus of records. They are arranged alphabetically by last name.
    - Rejection Letters and Rejected Proposals, undated (Box 7, Folder 607)
    - Akalaitis, Joanne, undated (Box 7, Folder 608)
    - Adams, Tessie Ann, undated (Box 7, Folder 609)
    - Ammon, Stefka, undated (Box 7, Folder 610)
    - Araiza, Alberto, undated (Box 7, Folder 611)
    - Aree, Elia, undated (Box 7, Folder 612)
    - Armstrong, Gordon, undated (Box 7, Folder 613)
    - Assante, Kariamu Welsh, undated (Box 7, Folder 614)
    - Attie, Shimon, undated (Box 7, Folder 615)
      Contains 19 slides.
    - Bachemin, Angelamia, undated (Box 7, Folder 616)
    - Belton, Don, undated (Box 7, Folder 617)
    - Benton, Suzanne, undated (Box 7, Folder 618)
    - "Black is Black Ain't" Unit, undated (Box 7, Folder 619)
    - Bardowitz, Gregg, undated (Box 7, Folder 620)
    - Breuer, Lee, undated (Box 7, Folder 621)
    - Buchanan, Nancy, undated (Box 7, Folder 622)
    - Burton, Gail, undated (Box 7, Folder 623)
    - Capers, Jerry, undated (Box 7, Folder 624)
    - Castro, Robert, undated (Box 7, Folder 625)
    - Children of War Promotional Material, undated (Box 7, Folder 626)
    - Chin, Daryl, undated (Box 7, Folder 627)
    - Cho, Seoungho, undated (Box 7, Folder 628)
    - Chong, Ping, undated (Box 7, Folder 629)
    - Chuma, Yoshiko, undated (Box 7, Folder 630)
    - This folder was omitted from the numbering sequence and does not exist., undated (Box 7, Folder 631)
    - Cohen-Cruz, Jan, undated (Box 7, Folder 632)
    - Conway, Merry, undated (Box 7, Folder 633)
    - Cortez, Reginald, undated (Box 7, Folder 634)
    - Cunningham, Kevin, undated (Box 7, Folder 635)
    - Delana, Steven, undated (Box 7, Folder 636)
    - Diamond, Liz; Picoult, Darcy, undated (Box 8, Folder 637)
    - Diggs, Peggy, undated (Box 8, Folder 638)
    - Girl Talk: Voices from Inside Juvenile Hall Compiled by Mezek Leimert, undated (Box 8, Folder 639)
    - Gonzalez, Anita, undated (Box 8, Folder 640)
    - Goode, Joe, undated (Box 8, Folder 641)
    - Graney, Pat, undated (Box 8, Folder 642)
    - Greanier, Mary-Ann, undated (Box 8, Folder 643)
    - Halleck, DeeDee, undated (Box 8, Folder 644)
    - High, Kathy, undated (Box 8, Folder 645)
    - Hoffbauer, Patricia, undated (Box 8, Folder 646)
    - Mueller, Lavonne, undated (Box 8, Folder 647)
    - Jackson, Homer, undated (Box 8, Folder 648)
    - Jones, Bill T., undated (Box 8, Folder 649)
    - Kamler, Richard, undated (Box 8, Folder 650)
    - Laurent, Marguerite, undated (Box 8, Folder 651)
    - Lock Down U.S.A., undated (Box 8, Folder 652)
    - Mauberry, Robert, undated (Box 8, Folder 653)
    - Menkes, Nina, undated (Box 8, Folder 654)
    - Open Wounds Divecchio, Don, undated (Box 8, Folder 655)
    - Ridge Theater; Zippi, Don, undated (Box 8, Folder 656)
    - Scott, Anna, undated (Box 8, Folder 657)
    - Shorr, Bill, undated (Box 8, Folder 658)
    - Tectonic Theater Project: Proposal for The Laramie Project; Kaufman, Moises, undated (Box 8, Folder 659)
    - Voices from the Invisible, or Being Poor; Divecchio, Don, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 660)
    - Wilson, Martha, undated (Box 8, Folder 661)
  - Subseries 2.10: Summary Report
    One file containing the bound report of all of the Institute's Activities for the 1999 season. The report contains information on the participants; results of entry and exit interviews and evaluations; a review of the Institute's mission, goals, and planning; and recommendations for future activities. The report is 84 pages plus appendices.
    - A Report on the Accomplishments of the Institute...Summer of 1999 Prepared by Bella Abaya (Box 8, Folder 662)
- Series 3: 2000
  This series comprises the records of all activities for the 2000 season--the final season of the Institute in this form. As in the previous series, the bulk of the records fall into two major groups: administrative files and applications. Administrative files contain materials on all aspects of running the Institute. Applications are divided in this series into those applicants who were appointed, tentative applicants who had passed the first and perhaps second screening, rejected applicants and applicants who passed an initial screening. There is also a group of applicant records that were received unclassified. They may duplicate applications in the other subseries but their status in the application process is otherwise unknown.
  Additional material present in this series includes the report on the 2000 season, here present unbound in a series of folders; a set of files dealing with the appointment protocol; and a set of miscellaneous project material.
  - Subseries 3.1: Administrative Files
    This subseries represents the bulk of administrative files for the year 2000. It includes records on the staff, budgets, accommodations, projects, schedules and other details of running the Institute. Within this subseries there is a particular concentration of material on the core audience program. Records concerning participating artists are included here as well unlike the previous series. The subseries is arranged alphabetically by folder title.
    - About IACD: History and Goals, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 663)
    - Air Conditioning, undated (Box 8, Folder 664)
    - Account Manager Application: Kindler, Peter, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 665)
    - Airport Directions, Welcome Signs, undated (Box 8, Folder 666)
    - Apartment Profiles, undated (Box 8, Folder 667)
    - Apts. Sublet Directly by the IACD, undated (Box 8, Folder 668)
    - Apts. 2000 Vacate List (Box 8, Folder 669)
    - "Apts. Wanted" Posters, undated (Box 8, Folder 670)
    - Apt. List by Artist, undated (Box 8, Folder 671)
    - Apt. Deposits, undated (Box 8, Folder 672)
    - Artist Profiles: Arrival and Departure, Space and Production Needs, undated (Box 8, Folder 673)
    - Cancelled Apts., undated (Box 8, Folder 674)
    - Apts.: #3 Concord Ave. Instructions for Renters, undated (Box 8, Folder 675)
    - Apts.: Correspondence, undated (Box 8, Folder 676)
    - Apts: Corporate Stay Housing, undated (Box 8, Folder 677)
    - Artists: Acosta, Julian, undated (Box 8, Folder 678)
    - Artists: Coleman, Chad, undated (Box 8, Folder 679)
    - Artists: Fleschler, Glen, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 680)
    - Artists: Harper, Francesca; Jefferson Margo, undated (Box 8, Folder 681)
    - Artists: Lee, Charlie, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 682)
    - Artists: Riddle, Kimber; Chae, Esther, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 683)
    - Artists: Scott, Dread, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 684)
    - Artists: Smelser,Joe, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 685)
    - Artists: Solomon, Alisa, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 686)
    - Artists: Tully, Patrick, undated (Box 8, Folder 687)
    - Artists: Williams, Patricia, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 688)
    - Boston Arts Around Magazine, undated (Box 8, Folder 689)
    - Budget, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 690)
    - Budgets, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 691)
    - Budget, Final, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 692)
    - Budget, Other Monies, undated (Box 8, Folder 693)
    - Calendar, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 694)
    - Cambridge Maps and Guides, undated (Box 8, Folder 695)
    - Cambridge Directory of Services and Information, undated (Box 8, Folder 696)
    - Company Assistant Application: Newcomer, Kate, undated (Box 8, Folder 697)
    - Company manager Application: Walker, Jollina, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 698)
    - Company Relations, undated (Box 8, Folder 699)
    - Contact Sheet--Staff, undated (Box 8, Folder 700)
    - Contact Information, Summer, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 701)
    - This folder was omitted from the numbering sequence and does not exist., undated (Box 8, Folder 702)
    - Contract Riders, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 703)
    - Core Audience Membership Forms, undated (Box 8, Folder 704)
    - Core Audience Membership Forms, undated (Box 8, Folder 705)
    - Core Audience Invitations, undated (Box 8, Folder 706)
    - Core Program: Border Ballad; Martinez, Ruben, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 707)
    - Core Program: Fat: Alfaro, Luis, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 708)
    - Core Program: Firestones; Azeda, Hope, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 709)
    - Core Program: Firestones; Azeda, Hope, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 710)
    - Core Program: Firestones; Azeda, Hope, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 711)
    - Core Program: Grief; Stimpson, Catherine, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 712)
    - Core Program: Hollow Space; Kennedy, Sheila, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 713)
    - Core Program/Dialogue: Hymns for Hagar, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 714)
    - Core Program: Lockdown; Scott, Dread, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 715a)
    - Core Program: Musical Prayers; Roche, Suzzy, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 715b)
    - Core Program: Piano; Smith, Anna Deavere, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 716)
    - Core Program: Silent Song; Bowers, Bill, 2000 (Box 8, Folder 717a)
    - Core Program: Skin; Williams, Patricia and Lake, Oliver, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 717b)
    - Core Program: Twilight Screening; Smith, Anna Deavere, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 718)
    - Core Program: Unfinished Stories; Harper, Jefferson, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 719)
    - Correspondence with Samantha Morgan, re: Internships, undated (Box 9, Folder 720)
    - Correspondence with Maia McAleavey, re: Job Positions, undated (Box 9, Folder 721)
    - Correspondence with Claire Fischer, re: Job Positions, undated (Box 9, Folder 722)
    - Correspondence with Benjamin Buckley and Maisie Tsui, re: Job Positions, undated (Box 9, Folder 723)
    - Damage Waiver Forms, undated (Box 9, Folder 724)
    - Dark Rooms, undated (Box 9, Folder 725)
    - Database Instructions, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 726)
    - Departmental Reports, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 727)
    - Departure Day Procedure, undated (Box 9, Folder 728)
    - Dialogue Series Contact List, undated (Box 9, Folder 729)
    - Dialogue Series, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 730)
    - Documentation and Evaluation, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 731)
    - Departmental Notes, Handwritten, undated (Box 9, Folder 732)
    - Financial Report--Company Mgmt, undated (Box 9, Folder 733)
    - Harvard Maps, undated (Box 9, Folder 734)
    - Harvard Museum Calendar, undated (Box 9, Folder 735)
    - Hotel, BandB List, 7/25/00, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 736)
    - Housing Appts. and Schedule, undated (Box 9, Folder 737)
    - Housing Leads, undated (Box 9, Folder 738)
    - Housing Notes and Correspondence, undated (Box 9, Folder 739)
    - Institute Floorplans and List of Bookings, undated (Box 9, Folder 740)
    - Intern Binder: Directions to Institute, undated (Box 9, Folder 741)
    - Intern Binder: Events Information and Flyers, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 742)
    - Intern Binder: Harvard/Cambridge Maps and Orientation Info, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 743)
    - Intern Binder: Intern Assignment List, Summer, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 744)
    - Intern Binder: IACD Communication and Contact Information, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 745)
    - Intern Binder: Intern Housing, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 746)
    - Intern Binder: Intern Names and Information, Summer, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 747)
    - Shameless Frenzy Intern Piece, undated (Box 9, Folder 748)
    - Intern Binder: Privileges, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 749)
    - Intern Binder: Requests, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 750)
    - Intern Binder: Orientation Food, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 751)
    - Intern Binder: Orientation Packets, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 752)
    - Intern Binder: Space Reservations, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 753)
    - Intern Binder: Orientation, Plannings, Schedules, 1999 (Box 9, Folder 754)
    - Intern Orientation, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 755)
    - Killip Rental Agreement, undated (Box 9, Folder 756)
    - Landlord Contact List, undated (Box 9, Folder 757)
    - Logistical Notes, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 758)
    - Meal Plan, undated (Box 9, Folder 749)
    - Miscellaneous Notes on Planning, undated (Box 9, Folder 760)
    - Other Related Organizations, Sites, undated (Box 9, Folder 761)
    - Payment Status of Employees, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 762)
    - Potential Production/Company/Marketing Assistants, undated (Box 9, Folder 763)
    - Presentation Reports, undated (Box 9, Folder 764)
    - Press and Marketing Associate, Job Description, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 765)
    - Press Release, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 766)
    - Production Contact Information, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 767)
    - Production Designers, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 768)
    - Production Directors, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 769)
    - Productions, Inc., 2000 (Box 9, Folder 770)
    - Production Ledger, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 771)
    - Production Manager: Bowin, Monica, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 772)
    - Production Receipts, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 773)
    - Production Receipts, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 774)
    - Production Schedules, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 775)
    - Props, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 776)
    - Promotional Materials (Originals), 2000 (Box 9, Folder 777)
    - Public Relations Candidates, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 778)
    - Managing Director Application: Jackson, Candace, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 779)
    - Reflection Week, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 780)
    - Rental Agreement, undated (Box 9, Folder 781)
    - Renter Information Sheet, undated (Box 9, Folder 782)
    - Resume for Housing Coordinator: Rebekah Durham, undated (Box 9, Folder 783)
    - Review of 1999 Housing Schedule, undated (Box 9, Folder 784)
    - Signage, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 785)
    - Schedule A, Orientation Schedule, 6/26/00, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 786)
    - Orientation Speech, undated (Box 9, Folder 787)
    - Arrival and Departure Schedule, undated (Box 9, Folder 788)
    - Sound Studios, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 789)
    - Space Inventory, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 790)
    - Spaces, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 791)
    - Spaces, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 792)
    - Spaces, Correspondence and Contacts, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 793)
    - Spaces, Floor Plans and Theater Specs, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 794)
    - Staff, Miscellaneous Contact Numbers, Resumes, Letters of Reference, undated (Box 9, Folder 795)
    - Staff: Waggener, John, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 796)
    - Staff Meeting Agendas, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 797)
    - Staff Meetings: June 13-June 30, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 798)
    - Staff Meetings: July 5-August 1, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 799)
    - Stage Manager Application: Stephens, Darcy, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 800)
    - Stage Managers, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 801)
    - Sublet Information, undated (Box 9, Folder 802)
    - Sublet Apt. Notes, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 803)
    - Summer Participants, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 804)
    - Telephone Bills, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 805)
    - Tenant Notes for Each Sublet, undated (Box 9, Folder 806)
    - Utility Payments, undated (Box 9, Folder 807)
    - Welcome: Transit Maps, undated (Box 9, Folder 808)
    - Welcome Letter, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 809)
    - Welcome Packet Inserts, undated (Box 10, Folder 810)
    - Welcome, Safety Packet, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 811)
    - Welcome to IACD, Summer, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 812)
    - Welcome: Directory, Contact Sheet, Schedule, undated (Box 10, Folder 813)
  - Subseries 3.2: Miscellaneous Project Material
    These files are assorted records and documentation of the 2000 session projects. Files relate to performers and to pieces. Arranged by topic.
    - Artist Budget: Mosakowski, Susan, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 814)
    - Artist Budget: Wija, Wayann, undated (Box 10, Folder 815)
    - Potential Artists: Brill, Robert, undated (Box 10, Folder 816)
    - Artist Budgets, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 817)
    - Artists Budgets and Proposals, 2000 (Box 10, Folder 818)
    - Class Action: Budget Proposal, Project Proposal, Press Releases, undated (Box 10, Folder 819)
    - Firestones: Hope Azeda, undated (Box 10, Folder 820)
    - Gray Matter: Lani Guinier and Tim Mitchell, undated (Box 10, Folder 821)
    - Lockdown: Dread Scott, undated (Box 10, Folder 822)
    - Ruben Martinez, Border Ballad, undated (Box 10, Folder 823)
    - Unfinished Stories: Francesca Harper, Margo Jefferson, Paul Miller, undated (Box 10, Folder 824)
    - Musical Prayers: Suzzy and Maggie Roche, undated (Box 10, Folder 825)
    - Skin: Patricia Williams and Oliver Lake, undated (Box 10, Folder 826)
    - Hymns for Hagar: Ysaye Barnwell, undated (Box 10, Folder 827)
    - Grief: Catharine Stimpson, undated (Box 10, Folder 828)
    - Press Clippings, 1998-2000 (Box 10, Folder 829)
  - Subseries 3.3: 2000 Overview
    Like the 1999 overview in Series 2, this report covers all the activities of the Institute for the Year including profiles of the artists, program operations, schedules of activities as well as administrative details such as fundraising catering arrangements and other logistics. This report is disbound and the sections arranged alphabetically by topic.